(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Cheongma Group's Open Competition
for New Designers)
(Episode 10)
(2026 New Designer Competition:
Application Desk)
(Cheongma Group's Open Competition
for New Designers)
So, this is where you are.
Just you wait.
I'll find you and make you pay
for what you did.
(Cheongma Group's Open Competition
for New Designers)
Open competition for new designers?
(Cheongma Group's Open Competition
for New Designers)
(Grand Prize: 50,000 dollars
and a position at Cheongma)
The grand prize is...
a position in the design office?
Well, look who it is.
It really is you, Ko Eun Seol.
Oh, right.
This is your family's company,
isn't it?
It's been a while.
How have you been?
Are you married?
No, not yet.
Then what about work?
I'm looking for a job.
I see. You're unemployed.
So what brings you here?
I told you. I'm looking for a job.
I want to work here.
You? At our company?
Why?
Is there some reason
I can't work here?
Did you even graduate
from high school?
You were expelled.
You have a good memory.
Or do you remember
because you got me expelled?
Whatever.
Let me give you some advice.
Dream on.
This isn't a place
someone like you can get into.
From what I've learned, Hae Ra,
you never know
what's going to happen in life.
So don't be so sure of yourself.
I may not know about other things,
but as long as I'm here,
you'll never get into Cheongma.
That much is certain.
Why do you hate me so much?
You really don't know?
Because you don't know your place.
You were just like this before.
How have you not changed at all?
And you're still
as rude and arrogant as ever.
Exactly.
Stop getting involved with someone
as rude and arrogant as me,
and just go your own way.
Don't waste your energy
on a lost cause.
I'm home.
- Hey.
- Hae Ra, hey.
Come here for a second.
Why?
Let me see your phone.
Why do you suddenly
want to see my phone?
We're curious what name
you saved us under.
What do you think?
I just have you saved
as Mom and Dad.
I knew it.
You know, this one young woman
had her dad in her phone...
as "My Dearest Dad,"
even with a heart.
Really? What young woman
is that thoughtful?
There was this young woman
I bumped into a few days ago,
and we accidentally
swapped our phones.
That's how she had her dad saved
in her contacts.
Her father must've saved
a country in his past life.
I'm so jealous.
I know, right?
But when I saw that,
it really touched my heart
for some reason.
So, Hae Ra,
you should reflect on that.
Just "Mom" and "Dad."
That's kind of cold.
Well, how do you and Dad
have me saved in your phones?
What?
See?
The apple doesn't fall far
from the tree.
Honey, really. Why start an argument
you know you can't win?
I was just jealous of her parents,
that's all.
Do you need something?
Ms. Joo.
Do you happen to remember
someone named Ko Eun Seol?
Ko Eun Seol?
You know, the girl I got expelled
back in high school.
Oh, her.
Why are you suddenly
asking about her?
Earlier, I ran into her
in the main lobby.
The main lobby?
Can you believe
she wants to work for our company?
She said that?
So I told her to keep dreaming.
I said it'll never happen
as long as I'm here.
What's on your mind?
Oh, it's nothing.
I mean, she was expelled
from high school.
How could she possibly get a job
at our company?
- It's just ridiculous.
- My thoughts exactly.
She still doesn't know her place.
This isn't worth eating.
A murderer like her? How could she?
In her dreams.
(Cheongchun Gositel)
(Cheongma Group's Open Competition
for New Designers)
(Cheongma's First
Blind Design Contest)
(Apply)
You're going to enter
the design competition?
Yes. But I can't quite do it
on my own.
I'm going to need your help,
Attorney Seo.
What can I do to help?
Well, the competition theme is
"The Rebirth of Cheongma."
And?
I need to analyze...
all of Cheongma's past collections
and design history,
but there's only so much
I can find online.
I see.
So you're saying you need
Cheongma's internal documents.
Yes. Is that possible?
But can looking at some documents...
really help you win
the designer competition?
Actually, I wanted to go
to art school.
I was told I had a real talent.
I earned every design certification
while on the inside.
I even had a mentor there.
Who was your mentor?
There was a famous designer
in there.
She was in for white-collar crime.
In that case, it sounds like
it's worth a shot.
All right. I'll see what I can do.
I'm sorry to ask for so much.
Hey, I told you.
This isn't just your fight,
Eun Seol.
This is a more approachable line...
(Planning Director, Cha Seok Jin)
Seok Jin. Let's go get lunch.
I ordered in.
Why would you order in?
Let's go eat out together.
I have a mountain of work to do.
(Planning Director, Cha Seok Jin)
But you don't have to work
through your lunch break.
A lot of people are watching me.
Some say I got here via connections,
and others say
it's all thanks to them.
I have to prove myself
with my skills.
I get the connections part,
but who said
it's all thanks to them?
Someone.
Was it Director Joo?
How did you know?
I can't believe her.
But it's true you have her to thank.
She pushed out Chief Choi
to get you that position.
What?
Anyway,
Director Joo can be scary,
so don't ever make an enemy of her.
Got it?
(Head of Legal Affairs,
Seo Hyun Jae)
Is this the Security Team?
This is Seo Hyun Jae, head of Legal.
I'm gathering evidence for
a brand IP infringement response.
I need access to the Archive Room,
but my key card isn't working.
The Archive Room has
a high security level,
so it requires
separate authorization.
Who has the authority to approve it?
The Chief of Planning.
As in Chief Cha Seok Jin?
Yes, I understand.
A temporary pass
for the Archive Room?
I need to collect evidence for
a brand IP infringement response.
This is rather sudden.
Has there been an issue
that warrants this?
We've received intelligence about
the overseas counterfeit market.
There are reports of a move
to openly copy Cheongma's designs.
Is that so?
All right.
I'll ask Security to issue you
a temporary pass.
Thank you.
So you're the head
of the Legal Team.
That's right.
We haven't been formally introduced.
I'm Cha Seok Jin,
the new Chief of Planning.
I'm Seo Hyun Jae.
Looks like I'll be working closely
with Legal from now on.
I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to it as well.
What's Team Leader Seo
been up to lately?
Why the sudden interest in him?
I heard Ko Eun Seol said
she wants to join our company.
I'm just wondering...
if Mr. Seo might be helping her
in some way.
Sure. I'll look into him.
I sent the temporary pass
by courier.
By courier?
Considering they deleted
the vehicle records,
they probably know I'm helping you.
So I thought it'd be best
to be careful.
Right. I see.
Also,
since they also know
what you look like,
try to avoid being seen
by the other employees.
Okay, I will.
By the way,
how did it go with your brother?
Did you clear up
the misunderstanding?
No.
How could a decade-long issue
be resolved so easily?
Anyway, thank you, Attorney Seo.
Of course.
I'm home.
Who are you?
Hello.
It's been a long time, Mr. Ko.
A long time?
Don't you remember him?
He's the lawyer who defended
Eun Seol ten years ago.
So, what brings you here?
I wanted to talk to you, Eun Guk.
I have nothing to say to you.
Do you want your sister
to be the killer?
Are you afraid to know you hated
your sister for ten years...
for nothing?
What did you just say?
If that's not it,
there's no reason to refuse to talk.
Fine. I'll hear you out.
Good, yes.
So, what is it that you want to say?
I hear you still think
your sister is guilty.
You need to get that straight.
Eun Seol didn't do it.
But what about the witness?
There was one, remember?
He committed perjury.
Perjury?
That's right.
Apparently, the guard took money
and was instructed to lie.
Who would instruct him to do that?
The actual killer, I'd imagine.
They must've needed someone
to take the fall for them.
Who was that exactly?
I don't know for sure yet myself.
But Eun Seol and I
will definitely find out.
Then why couldn't you
prove it back then?
You were Eun Seol's lawyer,
weren't you?
You should've proven it then.
I'm sorry.
It was the first case I handled
after becoming a lawyer,
so I was very inexperienced.
The witness's testimony
was so powerful,
and the trial was rushed through.
That must be why
you're still helping our Eun Seol.
Out of guilt.
Yes.
Don't forget to eat your vegetables.
Uncle.
Are you skipping
breakfast again today?
You eat up, Teun Teun.
I'll get going.
Uncle must still be mad at you, Mom.
Hyun Jae!
What?
Invite Eun Seol over sometime.
You don't have to force it.
I'm not forcing it.
Just ask her when she's free.
Make sure you do.
Yes, Eun Guk.
Where is that punk?
Who?
The punk who lied on the stand.
You mean Lee Jung Tae?
Why do you ask?
Where is he?
Eun Guk,
Eun Seol and I will handle this,
so you stay out of it.
Just tell me where he is.
Eun Guk, please.
I won't hang up until you tell me.
So just tell me already.
Where is that punk?
Attorney Seo!
He's staying at the Yeonju Motel
in Sillim-dong,
but you can't use violence
whatsoever.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Hello?
Eun Guk?
Eun Guk!
(Baggage Storage)
This is Room 2008
at the Yeonju Motel.
One sweet and sour pork
and two bottles of soju, please.
What the...
Are they kidding me? Darn it!
- It's Lee Jung Tae.
- Answer.
Do you have more business with me?
Are you messing with me?
I'm pretty sure I asked
for 100,000 dollars.
You should be grateful
you even got 10,000.
I was going to give you nothing,
but I took pity
on your pathetic life.
So you're calling my bluff?
I could go see Ko Eun Seol
right now, you know.
Go ahead.
What...
What's making you so confident?
Do you think I won't talk
because I'm an accomplice?
You're dead wrong!
Your mother is staying
with her sibling in Seosan.
What do you say?
Maybe I'll pay her
a visit right now.
What?
If you know what's good for you,
get on a plane to Vietnam
and disappear.
And don't try any funny business.
Good job.
You...
Darn, that was fast.
Lee Jung Tae?
Who are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
Which scum told you
to give false testimony?
Who was it? Tell me, now!
What are you talking about?
You don't know?
Then I'll make you understand.
How about that?
Are you starting to get it now?
Tell me. Who was it?
Who told you to frame my sister?
Hey. Get back here.
(Unregistered Card)
(Door Unlocked)
(The History Of Cheongma:
50th Anniversary Special Report)
Are you home?
- Yes.
- It's boiling out. Why the hat?
My gosh!
Eun Guk, what happened to your head?
It's nothing.
Grandma, why would you
just snatch my hat off?
Gi Han. Come out here!
Eun Guk came home
with his head split open.
What? What do you mean
his head is split open?
What happened?
Did you get in another fight?
Did you get into a fistfight again?
This time, it was for a good reason.
So don't give me a hard time.
What could ever justify
getting into a fistfight?
Wait, hold on.
Are you saying your head got hurt
because of Eun Seol?
It's not because of her.
If it's not because of her,
then what is it?
Good for you.
For once, you acted like
a proper big brother.
Your own son came home
with his head split open,
and you're praising him for it?
Give me Eun Seol's phone number.
What are you going to say to her?
This happened because of her.
She should at least pay
his hospital bills.
Come on, just give me her number.
There's no need for that.
This is more than enough
to cover the hospital bills.
What's this?
My gosh, how much is this?
It's 10,000 dollars.
Where did you get this money?
The guy took off, leaving it behind.
- What?
- The one who paid him to lie...
must've paid him off again.
Then this money...
Is it ours now?
No.
It's not ours.
It belongs to Eun Seol.
Why give her the money
you got your head busted open for?
Give it here.
Because of him,
Eun Seol spent ten years in prison.
This is for her pain and suffering.
Eun Guk!
Then what about all the suffering
I went through because of you?
At least that brat
did something right today.
What are you talking about?
Gosh, all that money...
The money.
Right.
So how is the competition going?
It's still early,
so we don't have many entries,
but the interest is very high.
And how do you know
the interest is high?
Daily website visitors
have increased tenfold,
and with hundreds of inquiries
hitting the Q and A board,
we've assigned dedicated staff.
The Cheongma competition is also...
consistently trending
in related online communities.
Is that right?
All right. Good work. You may go.
Yes, sir.
By the way,
evidence collection
for the brand IP infringement...
will be completed this week.
Evidence collection
for the brand IP infringement?
We've been doing that?
Wasn't this reported to you, sir?
I just assumed you knew.
Who's in charge of that?
The head of the Legal Team
said he was handling it,
so I even issued him
a temporary pass to the Archive.
Tell the head of Legal to come in.
Yes, come in.
You called for me, sir?
Word is you're collecting evidence
related to our brand IP.
What's that about?
Oh, that.
We got a tip...
that overseas competitors
are blatantly copying...
Cheongma's design patterns.
That's why, sir.
Why wasn't something so important
reported to me?
I was planning to report it
once we had all the evidence.
Right now, it's just a tip,
and I didn't want to confuse you
with inaccurate information.
I'll be the judge of that.
From now on,
if anything like this happens,
report it to me immediately.
Understood?
Yes, I understand.
- Aren't you going home?
- You go ahead.
Come on.
Are you working late again tonight?
There's no point
in you being in Korea at all.
What do you mean?
We haven't been on
a single proper date yet.
We see each other at work every day.
Why do we need to go on dates?
You told me we needed
to keep things professional at work.
After being so strict about that,
now you say we don't need dates?
Did I say that?
Fair enough.
But just bear with me
for a little while.
My dad should know
how hard you're working.
He'll acknowledge it
once I show him results.
All right.
Since you're trying so hard
to marry me,
I guess I can be patient.
I'm heading out then.
Get home safe.
(Planning Director, Cha Seok Jin)
I need to collect evidence for
a brand IP infringement response.
This is rather sudden.
Has there been an issue
that warrants this?
We've received intelligence about
the overseas counterfeit market.
There are reports of a move
to openly copy Cheongma's designs.
Is that so?
All right.
I'll ask Security to issue you
a temporary pass.
By the way,
evidence collection
for the brand IP infringement...
will be completed this week.
Evidence collection
for the brand IP infringement?
We've been doing that?
Wasn't this reported to you, sir?
I just assumed you knew.
(Chairman's Office)
Who's in there?
Come out. Now.
I said, come out.
(A Trap Called Desire)
I knew this would happen.
This is what you get
for taking in a stranger.
Grandma, what are you doing?
Don't tell me...
Why not let Eun Seol stay
in your annex then?
Do you know
when I first fell for you?
When did you start to like me?
I'm sorry to say this.
I'm afraid that's going to be tough,
Director Joo.
What do you think of Chief Cha
as a son-in-law?
What's in it for you?
Just be smart for once, please.
You seem to care more
for Hae Ra than I do.
I'm sorry, sir.
I overstepped my bounds, didn't I?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)